The End Ow... Ugh...
Hmm...
You should really have a
doctor take a look at that.
Yeah, yeah, I already know that...
But I want you to give me a bit
of first aid in the meantime.
Alright, take it easy.
Wait, Fugo, you're not gonna...
AHHHHH!
Have you lost your mind?
Did that just happen?
Holy shit, you sealed him
up like a freaking manga.
Hey, Narancia, you mind grabbing the
duct tape and wrapping up his midsection?
I'm on it.
This hack job isn't going
to get infected, is it?
Don't worry, you'll be fine.
It's actually kind of growing on me.
May I chime in?
Vagazzi, you've made me proud.
It's thanks to all of your efforts
that we made it to Capri alive.
Our would-be attackers have been neutralized
and are being held on the ship for now.
The obstacle has been cleared.
Then let's go!
There's no time like the present!
Our 10 billion lira treasure awaits!
Enough suspense.
Where'd you hide it?
A hidden safe at the bank? No.
You must have buried it in
some cave on the island.
I need you to wait a little longer.
Where's this coming from?
And why do we need to wait around?
Shh!
Could you wait a few?
There are still some people left in there.
Well, think you could
clean this place later?
So you must be La Toilette?
Huh?
What do you mean by that?
If your name was La Toilette, that'd make
this place your house, giving you a say.
After all, one calls the
shots in their own home.
Of course,
if this isn't actually your house,
then you really have no
business ordering me around.
What?
Hold it, moron!
What part of comeback
later don't you understand?
The hell?
Hey, what do you think you're doing, pal?
Knock it off!
What the hell, user?
Come on, I'll slice you apart! Wait!
Back off now, Narancia.
But I want to cut this fool!
Things aren't as they seem.
Huh?
That stern voice.
We've kept you waiting.
Gentlemen, bow your heads.
This is Mr.
Pericolo, a Cape from Passione.
I've come all the way here for
the 10 billion lira, Bucciarati.
I'll see you
next
time.
Fukatu no tamashi Dish yo?
Fighting cold!
I was the one who requested your
team travel here in the first place.
Please, everyone at ease.
You must be the rookie, huh?
Si.
Bucerates told me all about you.
You are with Passione now, which
makes you part of the Family.
I know we've only just met, but
by all means call me Mr. Pericolo.
I appreciate that, sir.
Oh, Sunny, pardon the
rough reception earlier.
She hates it when people touch
her without her permission.
Whatever.
Not cool!
It's yes, sir! Mr. Periculum.
If I may, why the elaborate disguise?
Oh, I have my reasons,
but I'll clarify later.
Before that, are you
positive that you have it?
The 10 billion lira
contribution to the Family?
Indeed.
Right here, in fact.
Back it up a bit!
What did you just say?
He said it's here! But where?
You're gonna have to be more specific.
Sorry, but all I see are urinals.
Whoa! What?
You hid it inside of that?
Well, I can't deny it was
secure, but holy moly,
if those guys knew what
they were pissing on!
Hmm, it's authentic.
This necklace alone is worth at
least seven or eight hundred million.
Bucciarati, I won't badger you for details
on how you obtain this cash of riches.
The Family cares not about your methods,
only that you follow
through with the funds.
Wait, hang on!
You're putting it away already?
Could I touch it a little?
I'd settle for a whiff!
This treasure is proof
incarnate that the man standing
before us today is one of
tremendous intellect and faith.
Well done, Bucciarati. You did it.
I hereby promote you to the rank of Cape.
Hey, did you hear that? He did it!
After all that,
Bucciarati's finally a Cape!
Since Polpo is no longer among the living,
you are now the successor to
the entirety of his territory.
You'll oversee all interests
related to the Family in Napoli,
including gambling, extortion,
port contraband, and restaurant
and hotel operations.
50 % goes to the Family.
The rest is yours for the taking.
Incredible!
So much power just like that!
With Bucciarati's smarts and charisma, our
little gang is gonna be rolling in dough!
Man,
it's like everything
started being set into
motion once that new guy Giorno got here.
He's a crazy good luck charm!
Oh, and there's one more thing.
I know you haven't had time to digest
your new duties as Polpo's successor.
But you should know he still
had one job left unfinished.
Naturally this responsibility
will now rest on your shoulders.
Are you willing to
accept his final mission?
It'll be a heavy burden to bear.
So I'm to finish what he started.
Be aware this is a direct
order from the boss.
The boss?
I see. Unreal.
Isn't this the same boss no
one's ever met in person?
And now we're getting
an order right from him?
That's right.
I'll deliver his words myself.
Your mission is to safeguard
the boss's daughter.
Laying down your lives if needed.
End of message.
His daughter? The boss?
Did he say daughter?
The daughter of the boss we were planning
on tracking down and eliminating?
Your safeguarding obligations begin now.
I'm turning her over to you
Turning her over.
Bucciarati.
Could that guy be?
No that woman.
She must be the boss's daughter.
Could that really be her I have to
Well, you know, that's fine.
Go ahead Trish
For now, stay by her side.
She is now our priority.
Bucciarati?
Her name is Trish Una,
and she's 15 years old.
The name Una comes from her mother, so
it has no association with the boss.
Trish has also never met the boss, so
she doesn't know anything about him.
Bucciarati, as you know, no one has
knowledge of the boss's true identity.
But of course, even someone
like the boss has a past.
His youth is especially intriguing.
Two months ago, in a hospital
in a small town in Calabria,
a woman named Donatella
succumbed to illness.
Just days before her death,
she initiated a frantic search
for a man named Solidonazo.
The man she was looking
for was Trish's father.
I assume it was a final act of love for a
daughter who'd soon be
left to fend for herself,
but...
She couldn't find him
because he doesn't exist.
It was just an alias, used by the boss in
his youth to conceal his true identity.
Am I right?
But he who seeks Naso
must exercise caution.
Anyone with any standing whatsoever in
Passione knows to take these words to heart.
To peer into the depths of the boss's
past is to defy the Family itself.
Word of Donatella spread like wildfire.
As you can imagine, with news
of a daughter, rumors exploded.
Of course, the hearsay
reached the boss too.
His resolution was unsurprisingly swift.
By way of several intermediaries,
he extended his order.
Upon Donatella's death, I
was to become her guardian.
He must have known instinctively.
He lived his life without
knowing she had ever existed,
yet suddenly he knew Trish was his own
flesh and blood.
Shortly after taking
Trish into my custody,
I discovered someone was attempting to hunt
her down and take the girl out for good.
Had the directive arrived
30 minutes later, I've no
doubt Trish's pursuers
would have taken her away.
They would have surely killed her.
But who'd do this?
Who would want to kill
the boss's daughter?
Traitors to the Family, of course.
And there's no telling how many there are.
They are attempting to
overthrow the boss and
take control of all the
drug trafficking routes.
Drugs again.
These idiotas have convinced themselves the
girl possesses secret intel on the boss.
They want intelligence
on how to topple the boss
when they carry out their coup.
But she has no such knowledge.
Trish is a vulnerable teen
in a strange new life.
How long will we protect her?
About seven days.
And likely it'll be
even shorter than that.
You'll be relieved of duty once
the boss eliminates the traitors.
Leave this island immediately
and place her under concealment.
This arrangement is top secret.
Only the boss and I know of it. Mr.
Pericolo, to clarify, this
mission was first Polpo's.
Isn't that right, Signore?
Which means...
That our enemies are stand-users.
I'd say that is a good guess, my boy.
In all likelihood they'll
be working in teams as well.
Unfortunately, we don't yet
know how many there are.
I don't possess a stand.
I've now done everything
I can to assist you.
If I obtain further intel,
I'll find a way to reach you.
Do you need something?
Yeah, uh,
will you be, well, um, are you the group
that'll be escorting me from here on out?
Yes, that is correct.
The six of us are here for you, Trish.
While you're with us, we will
protect you with our lives.
I see.
Then do me a favor.
Could you please take off
your jacket for just a minute?
You want me to take off my jacket?
But what for?
Don't worry, just take it off.
Trust me, I have no interest in
seeing you devoid of clothing!
You've made that clear.
I'm out of handkerchiefs,
so go buy me one.
While you're at it, get more nylons
and Givenchy blush number two.
Oh, and those nylons better be the
ones with the garter at the thigh.
And grab a copy of Vogitalia.
Mineral water would be nice too.
But it has to be from France.
I'd rather keel over than
drink that other stuff.
When you're done ogling the
scenery, get started on that list.
Protect the daughter of the boss, huh?
One minute we're hunting the bastard down,
and the next we're face to
face with his flesh and blood.
Still, this has to be done.
If we really follow through on this,
the boss will give Bucciarati the
same kind of trust he gave Polpo.
But if we fail, our story won't end well.
Everyone aboard this ship is
aware of that cruel reality.
What's with you?
Chill out, sweetie baby.
I'm just trying to show you some love.
Hey, come on.
Quit moving around so much.
can't you see i'm trying to read these
messages at 9 25 this morning officials
at the prison in naples were shocked to
discover that Papa had shot himself dead
on a stick i thought for sure Papa would
be the girl's guardian if it's not him
who is it then who'd stick their neck
out to look after that disappearing act,
Trish.
Well, I better get after it.
Find them, eh?
Who would be more capable of
protecting her than Polpo?
They definitely have to be a couple.
No one else would be assigned
to such an important job.
Them being a stand user
is also a no-brainer.
The question is, who the
hell checks all those boxes?
Groceries check surroundings clear.
let's see so i'm supposed to go
through here make a turn there end
up back on this street and then head
in the opposite direction right?
nice!
Narancia, you listening?
That's a list of groceries from the
group, along with everything else we need.
And these are the keys to the car.
Now listen up.
I have faith in you.
This will be a walk in the park.
One more thing.
No one has the faintest idea
our group is hiding out here.
Not even the vintners out front
are aware of our presence.
When you're done with the shopping,
I want you to retrace your path.
Then do it again more times
than you think necessary.
Also, make a U-turn every once in a while.
That way you'll know whether
anyone is tailing you.
After that, I want you to take the
car I left for you in the parking lot.
Then and only then do I
want you to come home.
No one should have any inkling that
we're looking after the boss's daughter.
But just in case someone
does know what we're up to,
this runaround strategy should
keep them off our trail.
You understand?
We need the things on the list.
That much is still true.
However it's absolutely imperative that
nobody finds our hideout crying out loud.
I get it I get it just leave everything
to me all right now repeat everything
we just discussed start to finish huh
well I buy all the stuff on the list then
drive around and around in a field until
that's the wrong answer quit screwing
around and get serious now tell me what
I said from the beginning you told me.
I need to drive around an
empty lot so I don't get dizzy.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Are you seeing this, Abbacchio?
Tell him to stop stabbing
me with the damn keys!
I never should have put him in charge
of shopping in the first place!
Whether you two man-babies want to keep
playing with keys is your own business.
As for me, I'm interested
in Narancia's stand.
If we're being followed, he'll put
an end to them before they know it.
That's why Bucciarati
gave him the task he did.
Long story short, I need to get my
ass back here without a soul knowing.
No stalkers allowed!
Something's off.
My eyes tell me I'm all by
myself, but my gut says otherwise.
And if that wasn't bad enough,
this car Fugo got me is
giving off some bad vibes too.
Come on now already I'm
dying to know where?
Oh where could you be heading to?
Narancia it came from here
now
like
I said where are you running off to?
Stranger you keep looking behind you?
Worried some big, bad boogeyman
is following you or something?
Just who the hell do you think you are?
You don't even act so scary.
Is that how you treat
someone asking you something?
I didn't realize you'd be so rude,
answering a question with a question.
Shut your face, freak!
I want you out of this car right now!
This isn't getting us anywhere.
You can call me Formaggio.
I'm part of the Family.
You are aware that Polpo
passed last night, aren't you?
This sucks ass.
Your trusty team...
Merida!
Talk about bad news!
I don't know how this guy found out
about our mission, but he's on to us!
Just great.
I wonder if he's a stand user.
Narancia, this is the rudest welcome ever.
What gives, amigo?
Where's Bucciarati and the
rest of your playmates?
No clue, friend.
How should I know where they are?
I'm not their keeper.
Did you check the restaurants around here?
This car you're using,
it's a rental, isn't it?
And Bucciarati is the renter.
Why would you be in this car
if you weren't aware of that?
Well?
I always drive around in his
cars, everyone knows that.
I'm 17, so I clearly don't have my own.
That's why I'm borrowing his. Hmm.
Oh yeah, did you hear the news?
Polpo's colossal corpse
is causing the mortician
trouble because he doesn't
know how to torch the thing.
There's no way to squeeze
him into the damn oven.
Guess I'll just have to hack that
fat calzone into tiny pieces!
You shut up! What?
Aren't you thinking the same thing?
Huh?
What?
Who are you talking to?
Wow, you totally fell for it!
You're such a disappointment!
Say, Narancia, answer something for me.
Why are you fools nowhere to be seen
while a Cape is being laid to rest?
Get to snitching already!
I don't have all day to
follow your ass around!
When I'm finished, kid, you
won't have a secret left!
Eat shit! Huh?
Better yet...
Drop dead!
What is that thing?
Little bummer!
So he's a stand user.
Get him, tiny feet!
Damn you!
Look at what you did to me, bastardo!
I'm bleeding!
How dare you hurt me!
I'll kill you!
Freaking hell!
This guy's a psycho!
Die! Die! Die! Die! Damn!
He doesn't quit!
I'll slaughter you!
This crazy kid's
completely blown a gasket!
He's shooting everything
in sight like a madman!
And I'm stuck inside this
tin can with nowhere to hide!
Staying in this car's gonna do me in!
That's the bomb!
Blow him away, little bummer!
How do you like that?
Did it feel good?
You a pile of ash yet? Ow!
Damn it! We get him?
What? Where'd he go?
Did the blast knock him
into the stratosphere?
No, just not a piece of him left!
Where'd he go?
You're so oblivious, kid.
I'm right under your nose.
I can micro-fy myself.
That's my very secret weapon!
My stand is called Tiny Feet, And all the
other guys said it wasn't worth anything.
They can talk shit till
they're blue in the face.
But personal talent is
all about how you use it.
What the hell?
I don't see him anywhere.
This is ridiculous.
How'd he just disappear?
Is he here?
The same damn thing happened when
he first showed up in the car.
You can look around to
your heart's content.
I'm gonna buy some time while you
parade around looking like a fool.
Huh?
Huh.
It's a chick.
What do you know?
The bastard's buying stuff for a chick.
He's got nylons and lipstick in there.
There's even some designer blush.
Who's all this shit for?
This Kagakatsu's mom?
This big sis?
No way.
Women are super picky
about stuff like this.
They buy their own makeup and clothes.
The only chick who'd entrust a
guy with this kind of thing is one
who thinks they would be in mortal
danger if they went outside.
This all stinks to high heaven.
It's looking like my instincts
were spot on after all.
The ones chosen to protect the boss's
daughter was Bucciarati
and his backscratchers.
It has to be them.
I will find their hiding place.
And the best part is Narachi
is going to show me how.
My power should be working
its magic on him any second.
That bastard's gotta be
around here somewhere.
I know he's waiting to
follow me back to the others.
Let him try!
I'm gonna shake off this
stalker and get back to base!
And if he tries to get
in my way, he's dead!
This mission is in the bag!
Thank you.